All your cars were faster and more expensive than mine.
But did you ever beat me, you idiot?
That's different, because you're nuts.
Did I ever say that my son is normal?
5. 4. 3...
--Go for it!
Go!
Don't wag your tail!!
But the AE86 doesn't have the acceleration.
It's OK to lose a little at the beginning.
There're less straights and more sharp corners later on.
Then my boy is going to show off.
The mighty GTR is leading all the way.
The AE86 can't come near it on the straights.
He may catch up on the corners.
but he has no chance to get near the GTR.
They're coming into the curves.
The AE86 is gaining,
but the GTR's turns are really precise.
The AE86 has changed tactics! It's starting to drift.
They're getting closer at the center of the curve.
The AE86 is attacking those corners fast!
The cars almost touched each other
as they drifted out!
Is your boy really that good?
A few years ago, my boy told me he needed glasses,
so I took him to an optician.
But his eyesight turned out to be 20/20.
I said to him: "Hey, kiddo,
I'll kick your ass if you're playing around!"
And he told me that, when he drives,
everything else
gets slower and slower.
Only then did I knew
that he was getting faster and faster.
"I lost at this corner last time. It won't happen again."
The AE86 is right on the GTR's ass!
Unbelievable!
The AE86 tried to overtake him,
but the GTR blocked the lane.
Hey! That's cheating!!
Are you out of your mind??
The AE86 didn't pass him,
but they're getting closer.
The AE86 is looking for a chance.
If what you said is true, then Takumi will win for sure?
It all depends on...
the last 5... consecutive hairpins.
They're at the last 5 hairpins and the AE86
isn't slowing down at all.
He can't pass at this speed!
The AE86 has passed the GTR at the inner curve!
Can the GTR catch up
at the remaining hairpins?
The GTR is slowing down! The AE86 has won!
Some driving style you've got.
Weren't you up the hill?
How did you get down here so quick?
I heard you went pass him on the ditch. Is it true?
I want to race you too. You've got time?
I'm sorry. I raced tonight because
my dad asked me to.
I don't think there'll be a next time.
Maybe you'll change your mind tomorrow.
It's done.
I've raised you right. You make me proud...
Hey, come on!
What is it?
Nothing.
What's with the towel?
It's the sun.
Don't be shy.
Is it because I'm wearing a bikini?
Of course not.
Where did you get those scars, Takumi?
These scars are...
They're from my dad.
Dad started drinking after mom left us.
He'd beat me up whenever he's drunk.
Disgusting, huh?
I think you look sexier that way.
A real man gotta have a few scars on his body.
I can't stand those sissies with smooth skin!
I really like this one here.
I got that three years ago.
This one is from last week.
Does it hurt?
And this one?
That's a mosquito bite.
You're such a kidder!
We're here.
You're a really good driver, Takumi.
I always get carsick on long rides,
but I didn't even need to take my pills today.
That's good then.
I had a great time today. Thanks a lot.
Sure...
Bye.
You know what a god is?
A god is human too,
but he can do things other people can't do.
So, please save me, God.
Please save my car too.
Have a seat.
What's with our "world champion", Boss?
He just bought an AE86.
What about Takumi?
That's easy. He's in love.
What's with you today?
You wouldn’t get it.
Of course I would!
You're a man, so it's either cash or chicks.
What are we doing here?
You said you'd teach me how to drive.
When did I say that?
Who cares? I'm going to drive downhill
as fast as I can.
Give me a few pointers.
Since I'm smart, I'm sure I can catch on fast.
Let's go then. It's gonna be quick.
Are you buckled up?
Car behind you.
Why's he driving so fast for?
He can't wait to get laid or what?
Turn on the hazard lights. Let him pass.
He hit us!
What's with him??
Sorry, I thought it was the AE from the tofu shop.
But it's just a piece of junk.
Hey, kids.
Shouldn’t you be sleeping at this hour?
Go home and go to bed.
He means you.
Did you see his bandanna? He must be gay!
I bet you he's looking for boys up there to...
Junk... Total junk.
I’ll drive!
Say something. What do you have in mind?
Didn't you see that he was trying to kill us?
So what?
And he said your car is a piece of junk.
Let him say what he wants. We don't care!
Hey, brake...
Use the brakes, yo!
The brakes!!
Itsuki, what's with your car?
What about it?
It doesn't brake when it enters a corner.
All four wheels are off the ground,
and it almost overturns when it exits a corner.
So why are you still driving so fast??
I gotta catch that asshole.
I wanna go home!! Daddy!!
Daddy!!!
Itsuki, are you all right?
Are you sure?
OK?
Takumi, what have you done?
I'm sorry. I wrecked Itsuki's car. I'll pay for it.
I'm not talking about that! Do you know
the guy last night is a member
of the Emperor Team?
He's a professional racer.
You've beaten his EVO with this piece of junk.
Are you out of your mind?
But it's exactly the same car as my dad's.
How could it be the same?
Your dad has spent so much time and effort
on his car.
It took him a month just to find
the right suspension!
This piece of crap here?
Only an idiot like my boy would get conned
into buying it!
Where's Itsuki?
Some "world champion" he is.
One spin and he's been puking nonstop.
You know any other guy that gets carsick?
You're different, Takumi.
You have a chance to become an ace racer
one day.
Keep it up.
Hey.
What? You dropped your money?
The suspension. Did it really take you
one month to fix it?
Why so long?
It's not just the suspension.
I had to test the tires, the brakes,
drive train, balance between front and rear...
A month was about right.
Is it really fun being a racer?
Why? You wanna be one?
I dunno.
You dunno?
Then come on in and help make tofu!
Your friend's been helping me for the whole afternoon.
My friend?
You don't have to do that!
It's no trouble at all.
Please have some tea, Uncle.
The tofu is all done. I made some dim sum too.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Takumi! You're back!
How come you're here?
Look who's talking!
You haven't called me once since our last date,
so I came to see you.
Natsuki, where's the dim sum?
I'll get it for you.
It's so nice having a girl in the house.
Especially with a skirt like that!
If only it's two inches shorter...
You should’ve called me first.
I called you lots of times,
but either you're at work or you're asleep.
Your dad is a nice guy.
He ain't a nice guy.
But I've talked to him on the phone a lot.
He really cares about you, did you know that?
You've talked to him on the phone?!
Something wrong with that?
What did he say?
Uncle told me you wanna be a racer.
I never said that.
He also told me that, if you try hard enough,
you'll one day become a world class racer.
Someone once told me that
the most important thing is to find a world to belong to.
Only then will we realize that life is meaningful.
Takumi... I think for you, that world is racing.
Who told you that?
My...my uncle.
Your uncle?
Ever since my father died,
he's been taking care of me and my mom.
I thought it was my dad.
I knew he couldn’t be that deep.
So who is this uncle, Natsuki?
"The most important thing is to find a world to belong to.
Only then will we realize that life is meaningful.
If you try hard enough,
you'll one day become a world class racer.
Takumi... I think for you, that world is racing."
You deliver tofu at this hour?
Something wrong with your car?
Wrong?
I'm tuning it.
I said I wanna race you, remember?
I never said I would.
If I ask you now, would you say yes?
I wanna ask you...Coordinating the suspension
and the tires...
Does it really take a whole month?
- You wanna know? - Yeah.
First, the engine. It's crucial to
increase the barometer of the turbocharger,
but you gotta keep an eye on the input air volume.
And the exhaust valve needs to match it too.
Suspension has to be tuned based on hardness,
shock absorption,
the tires' size and their angle to the road,
plus the lower arm bar and tower bar.
Then you fine-tune it based on the computer data.
Your dad is incredible.
If I were to retune it, it would take me
at least 6 months.
Your car has been tuned to its optimal level.
Simply put...
It's perfect.
So my old man is really that good.
However, every car has its limits.
One day, you're gonna want more from your car.
Just get another one.
But I only like my AE86.
So, when's our race?
3 weeks from now. Saturday.
Why so long?
You said it took 3 weeks
to retune your car, right?
That's him!
Got it.
Be careful. He's very fast on the corners.
So? It's just an AE86.
You OK?
I forgot to tell you. This is just a tofu delivery car.
You can't race us in this.
You could get hurt, got it?
That's right. You guys are professional racers.
Of course you look down on us street racers.
Professional or street doesn't matter.
We're all racers.
Right, you beat me once, didn't you?
You remember?
Wanna win again?
Sure, call me. You have my team's number.
Is the AE87 out yet?
It's up to AE89 already, I think.
Just talking, no hitting.
Hitting your kid in public will be very traumatic to him.
Shut your mouth!
Tofuman...
Just talking, no hitting.
Hitting your kid in public will be very traumatic to him.
I'm going home.
Are you still upset about losing?
I challenged Kyouichi, the guy who beat you,
to a race in 3 weeks.
You're invited.
If you don't have another car, I do.
Thanks, but I only wanna drive my own car.
Call me if you change your mind.
Want some cheesecake? It's delicious!
Natsuki brought it for you.
When was she here?
She's going away for a couple of weeks,
but she'll call you later.
What else did she say?
Was she supposed to say something else?
Hey! Hey!!
You're gonna eat the whole cake??
You'll stuff yourself to death!
Tofuman, your AE86 is already an antique.
Might as well switch to a new car. Why fix it?
Don't tell me you gonna put THAT
into the AE86?!
Isn't this a beauty?
But this is a race car engine.
You wanna go to jail?!
You're nuts.
Catching roaches, Itsuki?
No, looking for my old man.
He's been gone for days, just like you.
Customer.
That sucks. He's not young anymore.
He can't just leave his business like this.
That's irresponsible!
What'll happen to me if it goes bankrupt??
It's good that I've been living on my own,
otherwise I wouldn’t be this chubby.
Boss?! What happened??
Uncle, what did you do now?
We went for a spin at Mount Akina.
Is he down yet?
Coming.
Sounded like a high rpm.
But when it's entering the corner, it's too slow.
Hop in.
I’ll only show you once.
Watch carefully. Pay attention to the new tachometer.
Its power won't become obvious
until it's above 11,000 revs.
Sit tight. I wanna drive faster.
Miya...
That Kaiseki dinner was delicious, huh?
Not bad.
That's good.
Thanks so much for taking care of me
while I puked for two days straight.
You were like a goddess who saved me.
You're nuts.
I'm serious.
I believe in gods.
A god is human too,
but he can do things other humans can't do.
That's why he's a god.
But do you know that
a god also have the same urges as us humans?
What're you trying to say?
Most humans would...
sometimes go to
this love hotel and...
Since you're also in the "fill it up" business,
Miya, I'm sure you wouldn’t mind...
Pervert!
Natsuki?!
What the hell..?
I test-drove with my dad yesterday.
Turns out it's got a new tachometer.
I just found out yesterday.
Imagine. AE86, 250 horsepower.
You know how fast is 250 hp?
I did Mount Akina at 150kph...
It only took me a little more than 3 minutes.
Amazing, huh?
I really wanna tell everyone. You...
and Natsuki.
No need.
No need for what?
No need to tell Natsuki.
Takumi.
There's something I... I wanna tell my best friend.
Who's that?
You.
Go ahead.
I saw Natsuki...
Going into a love hotel with a guy.
--Love hotel? --Love hotel.
Are you sure?
It only costs 30,000 yen to bang her.
What did you say?
30,000 yen to bang her!
Your girl is a hooker!
What're you talking about??
I'm trying to help you and you hit me?!
Go to hell!
I've known you since 7 and you hit me over a whore??
Don't!
Stop it!
Come, hit me!
Go ahead, hit me!
Takumi, stop it!
Let's talk!
Why fighting?
Pull him back!
Stop it, boy!
Stop fighting...
Takumi!
Why did you hit him, you jerk?!
That's right, I'm a jerk! I jerk off too!!
Hello? It's me.
I shouldn’t have called your girl a whore.
I'm sorry.
Did you forget? Today is Saturday.
Everyone is waiting for you and your AE86.
Hello.
Hello?
It's me.
What's up?
I've been looking for you.
I've been in my hometown.
I'm boarding the train now. I'll be back tonight.
I'm racing at Mount Akina tonight.
I'll come see you right after the race, OK?
No...Why don't I come see you tomorrow instead?
The train is here. Talk to you later.
Natsuki, I really wanna see you.
Natsuki.
I've really enjoyed your company
this past 2 weeks, thanks.
Did I give you enough money last time?
It's better that we don't see each other
after tonight.
I don't wanna be like this anymore.
I don't wanna see you again.
I want to forget about all this.
All I want now is to be with Takumi.
Isn't it a bit too much, broomhead?
I know Ryousuke well.
I will never lose to the same guy...
twice.
Shit, I hope I didn't hurt him too bad.
You should talk.
Your nose has been bleeding for days.
See? There you go again.
Will this become a monthly thing
like your period?
What're we waiting for?? Everyone's here!
What's the rush?
I'll give him 5 minutes.
Doesn't really matter if he comes.
Tonight is between you and me.
Block the road. The race will begin in 5 minutes.
Wait! A car is coming!
It's the AE86!
We never had so many girls at our races back then!
That's right.
This is a ladies-only zone, pops. Take a hike.
It's coming!
So you've resurrected this piece of junk?
Way to go, tofu boy!
And where's your car, the one you crashed?
Tofu boy, you wanna go first?
No need. Just drive fast. I got other things to do.
Wear this.
No need.
Ryousuke's got something to tell you.
Listen, Takumi. Kyouichi is a professional,
but all professionals have their weaknesses...
You don't need to teach me. I'm gonna beat him.
What about me?
I'll beat you too.
The road is clear. We can start at any time.
Repeat: We can start at any time.
GO!!
All three cars took off at top speed.
Kyouichi's E3 is leading,
followed by Ryousuke's FC.
The AE86 is last.
They've past the first corner.
Both Ryousuke and Takumi made their best
lap time.
Everyone's faster when they're racing a pro.
What are you doing?
This is called "strategy".
The FC suddenly lags behind right before the tunnel.
I wonder what Ryousuke had in mind?
The speed is unbelievable!
All three cars exceeded 100 kph at the corner just now!
The AE86 is waiting for a chance
to overtake the E3 at the next corner.
Step on it, Takumi!!
Give it back! What's wrong with you??
What's wrong with YOU?? This is a race!
You gotta yell at a race!!
This is it.
They overtook him!
The E3 has hardly any room and
both the FC and AE86 used the ditch
to overtake the E3!
Let me explain, little girl.
In street racing, a professional’s common weakness
is to leave some open space when taking a right corner.
Step on it, Takumi!
Takumi, it's just you and me now.
What about the E3?
I'll block it for you.
Better watch your own ass.
The AE86 and FC both managed to pass a pro!
Who could’ve thought?
But the E3 is not out of it yet!
Although they use different tactics,
the FC and AE86 are way too fast
in the corner drifts.
Catching up to them will not be easy.
Step on it, Takumi!
Attention, everyone!
A vehicle has just left the national park
and it's heading up the mountain!
A car is coming towards you. Get ready to slow down!
Kyouichi is ignoring the warning! He's trying to overtake!
Should we block him?
Too late.
The E3 has crashed! The E3 has crashed!
The AE86 and FC passed through. They're still racing!
Is he OK?
Forget him.
Kyouichi! Are you OK??
They're at the 5 consecutive hairpins.
Can the FC pass here?
"The AE86 is at its Limits.
Now it's my turn."
The FC overtakes the AE86!
There's only 1km left!
I don't think the AE86 can make it.
What the hell?!
I knew it.
You knew what??
Takumi has never taken the lead before.
Ryousuke's car is powerful, but he still
stayed behind Takumi
because he wants to learn his moves and then overtake him.
So it's over for Takumi?
Not necessarily.
You've been driving by yourself all these years.
You've never competed with anyone.
Remember.
Don't pay attention to the competition itself.
Ignore other racers.
The one you need to beat is yourself.
They're almost at the finish line and the
AE86 hasn't given up yet!
It's still right behind the FC.
The FC missed its lane going into the corner!
Can Ryousuke withstand the pressure from the AE86?
The "pressure" comes from the tires.
Even though the car is retuned to 250 hp,
the FC is still too powerful.
But as time drags on, the tires won't hold up,
and the car can't drift all the way.
That's why the last 2 corners are the most
crucial of all!
There they come!
They're almost at the finish line!
The mighty FC still has the edge.
Looks like the outcome is clear.
The FC slows going into the corner!
The AE86 is taking the inner lane.
Can it overtake?
The AE86 has won!!
The AE86 is the ultimate
racing god of Mount Akina!
All right!! He did it!!
He won!!
I've lost.
So, what now? Any plans?
Nothing. What about you?
I'm gonna set up a new race team.
Are you interested?
Dunno. Gotta go.
Takumi! I really want you on my team.
Sleep on it.
We'll see.
Takumi!
Takumi! Takumi!
"The most important thing is
to find a world to belong to."
"Only then will we realize that life is meaningful."
"Takumi... I think for you, that world is racing."
Well? Did you lose?
Hey. Hey!
Let's have a drink!
Son of a bitch.
Itsuki, I'm sorry.
Hey, Ryousuke. It's me, Takumi.
I...
I want to be on your team.